I really can't stand you.
真受不了你
Every time, I have to heal you. Such a hassle.
每一次都搞得這麼麻煩
Your way of fighting is too crazy.
硬要用亂來的方式戰鬥
Sorry for bothering you all the time, Fred.
抱歉總是勞煩你 弗雷德
If it weren't for you, I would have died a long time ago.
沒有你 我早就翹辮子了
Of course.
廢話
But you're not the only one who causes trouble.
更何況又不是只有你
It's just that you are more troublesome than others.
只是你比別人更會給我添麻煩
Take it.
拿去
What is this?
這是什麼東西
If it's some minor magic,
如果是瑣碎的魔法
that talisman can nullify it.
那個驅邪符能夠使其無效
You'll be more secure with it, won't you?
拿著也比較放心吧
Really? Thanks, Fred.
真的嗎 謝啦 弗雷德
Ouch.
好痛
Please, can you save me some trouble?
拜託你讓我省一點事好嗎
Really. Fred just isn't honest.
真是的 弗雷德就是不坦率
If only he wasn't so rigid.
如果他可以更圓滑就好了
Like his way of speaking, for example.
例如講話方式之類的
But Leo also has issues.
但是雷奧也不對
That guy is too brazen.
那傢伙太厚臉皮了
He causes others to worry, but he is completely unaware.
害別人擔心得要命 卻渾然不覺
-Because he's too strong, he doesn't understand others' feelings. -Does it look good on me?
-因為他太強 反而不懂別人的心情 -我戴著好看嗎
-Fred will lose his temper sooner or later. -You don't need to wear it, keep it.
-弗雷德遲早也會發飆吧 -不必戴上 收起來
You're so observant, Yuria.
妳觀察得真仔細 尤莉亞
Anyway, they can still flirt with each other.
反正他們還能打情罵俏
-Hey you. -I don't think it's a problem for now.
-我說你啊… -目前不成問題
-What's the matter, Fred?
-怎麼了 弗雷德…
-You said flirting…
-打情罵俏
If something goes wrong between them,
萬一出事了
you must mediate for them.
就必須由你出面幫他們調解
Me?
我嗎
I really can't handle it.
我實在承擔不起啊
Please, Max.
拜託你囉 麥克斯
LABOR ROOM
(分娩室)
It seems like a big problem has occurred with the heroes.
勇者他們那邊好像出大事了
No time to care about them now, Sara.
現在沒時間管他們 莎拉
I've got a big problem here too.
我這邊也是出大事了
Can you hold on a bit longer?
還可以嗎 再撐一下就好
(Level 1 Demon Lord and One Room Hero)
《Lv1魔王與獨居廢勇者》
(Episode 11: Hero, Utterly Defeated)
(#11 勇者 滿臉塵土)
W-What? Something flew past.
什…什麼 有東西飛過去了
This is…
這是…
Are you a frog?
你是青蛙嗎
Who is this guy?
這傢伙是誰啊
I think I've seen him somewhere.
好像在哪裡看過他
Isn't this person… Hero Max?
是不是…勇者麥克斯
Really?
真假
Has he turned into this kind of old man?
他變成這種大叔了嗎
Ten years ago, he was…
十年前明明是…
What the hell. It hurts so much.
搞屁啊 痛死我了
I wish I hadn't come.
早知道就不來了
It's not good at all, damn it.
根本沒好事 該死的
Minister,
大臣
Chief Fred is the only one fighting for our country. What do you think?
現狀只有弗雷德長官為我國犧牲奮戰 您有何看法
It's not just him who's fighting for our country.
我並不認為僅有他犧牲小我
Just in case, the kingdom's army is standing by.
以防出狀況 王國軍已在待命
What do you mean by 'just in case'?
具體來說是什麼樣的狀況
Are you suggesting there's a risk to the homeland?
意思是有可能危害王國本土嗎
No, our kingdom's citizens' safety or interests will not be threatened.
不 絕不會威脅到 王國國民的安全或利益
-Please rest easy and carry on as usual… -Look!
-請各位安心 照常生活… -快看
Minister, just now,
大臣 就在剛才
Max appeared before Leo and Fred.
麥克斯出現在雷奧與弗雷德面前
See, girl. I told you so.
看吧 小妹妹 我說中了吧
I-It's amazing.
太…太棒了
Next, all Max has to do is stop Leo…
接下來只要麥克斯阻止雷奧…
Will things really go that smoothly?
事情會那麼順利嗎
Even if the current Max can win this battle,
即使現在的麥克斯能贏這場戰鬥
I don't think he'll blindly obey the kingdom.
我也不認為他會對王國唯命是從
Ignore her.
別管那傢伙
Look, it's about to start.
快看 要開始了
What are you doing here at this point?
事到如今你跑來幹嘛
Do you want to be the heroic savior of the kingdom's crisis?
是想當解救王國危機的勇者大人嗎
Kingdom's crisis? Don't flatter yourself.
王國的危機 少自大了
Do you think your existence is so great?
以為自己的存在那麼了不起嗎
Even if I have to oppose both of you,
即使要與你們為敵
I will fight to protect this land.
我也會為了保護這片土地而戰
You talk a good game.
嘴上說得那麼好聽
In essence, you've illegally occupied our territory with thugs.
說穿了只是集結一群小混混 非法占據國土
The one who wants to seize land is the kingdom.
想不當奪取土地的是王國
You know that very well, right?
你也很清楚吧
Shut up, you two idiots!
吵死了 兩個混蛋
Who cares about the kingdom or the republic?
管他什麼王國跟共和國
You guys talk a lot of crap.
講一堆廢話講個不停
I've had enough of you.
簡直受夠你們了
I might as well take you both down,
乾脆兩個一起幹掉
so I don't have to see you in the future.
免得我以後還要看到你們
That's the reality.
實際上不過就是這樣
Get ready for a fight to the death.
準備要開始殺得你死我活囉
You say I'm talking crap?
你說廢話
What are you joking about?
開什麼玩笑
What does a loser like you, who is out of touch with society, understand?
你這種和時代脫節的輸家懂什麼
If you don't understand, don't pretend to.
別說得好像你什麼都知道
Yeah, I don't understand.
對啊 我就是不知道
How would I know your difficulties?
你們的苦衷 我哪知道
I'm just pissed off, so I'm going to beat you up.
我就是不爽到想痛扁人
It's as simple as that.
只是這樣罷了
Idiot, go to hell, moron.
蠢蛋 去死吧 白痴
Although I'm not sure what's going on,
雖然不知道是怎麼回事
it seems that you're not here to support Fred.
但看來你並不是來幫弗雷德助陣
That's not necessarily a bad thing.
那也未嘗不可
After all, the last one standing is the winner.
反正最後仍站著的人就是贏家
It's simple. It's good.
簡單明瞭 挺不錯的
Come on, Max, Fred!
來吧 麥克斯 弗雷德
You two fools!
你們這兩個笨蛋
I think you're all doomed if you don't reincarnate.
不到死是治不好的
That's amazing,
太精彩了
these images are extremely valuable.
這段影像相當珍貴
Even though we can do nothing but watch.
雖然我們只能袖手旁觀
Seman, what do you think?
塞曼 你覺得呢
Perhaps this is retribution for our actions.
是我們的所作所為帶來的報應
What's up with you, Max?
怎麼啦 麥克斯
You're slowing down.
動作變遲鈍了
Shut up!
少囉嗦
Huh?
咦
You're pontificating over there, even brought out the Sacred Sword.
在那邊高談闊論 連聖劍都拿出來
What's with you, Max?
你卻是那副德性 麥克斯
You're making a lot of noise.
吵死了
Don't forget it's been ten years.
別忘了已經過了十年
My skills can't be as agile as a monkey.
總不會永遠都像猴子一樣活蹦亂跳
Aren't we the same age?
我們不是同年嗎
Shut up.
你給我閉嘴
You disappoint me deeply.
簡直失望透頂
You're not a hero.
算什麼勇者
Utterly foolish.
愚蠢至極
You can't go on living in shame.
別再繼續活著丟人現眼
I might as well send you off with my own hands.
不如由我親手超渡你
Max.
麥克斯
Is he still alive?
他還活著嗎
-What's wrong? -Did you see it?
-怎麼了 -看到了嗎
It's no use.
行不通
I have no chance of winning.
毫無勝算
I was so reckless that I shocked myself.
魯莽到連自己都傻眼
I actually wanted to fight head-on.
居然想要從正面蠻幹
We must not give up!
絕不能放棄
Lord Behmas,
貝…貝赫瑪斯大人
please kill these guys.
請您殺了這些傢伙吧
We must not give up!
絕不能放棄
What do you mean we must not give up?
什麼絕不能放棄
Cut the pep talk, Max.
精神喊話就免了吧 麥克斯
How do you intend to fight your way out of this situation
面對這種龐然大物
in the face of such a behemoth?
你打算如何殺出一條血路
The enemy is flying around, your swords aren't hitting,
敵人飛來飛去 你們的劍也砍不中
our attack spells are weakening,
我們的攻擊咒語效果越來越弱
we're insane to come here
簡直是瘋了
and fight this kind of opponent.
還跑來找這種對手開打
Don't worry, I'll be the shield.
大家放心吧 由我當盾牌
You always make me heal you when you play shield.
就說你每次當盾牌 都是靠我幫你治療
How many more times can you use the healing spell?
大概還能用幾次復原咒語
At most four or five times.
頂多四到五次吧
The situation is getting worse.
狀況越來越糟
Really, so I've been saying not to engage with this kind of opponent.
真是的 所以我才說不要跟這種對手開戰
Stop nagging about the past.
事情都過去了就不要再碎碎念
Max said we must not give up.
麥克斯都說了絕不能放棄
No matter what, we have to keep fighting until the last moment.
我們無論如何都要 堅持戰鬥到最後一刻
Yuria.
尤莉亞
You're right, Yuria.
說得沒錯 尤莉亞
I believe in Max and in you guys.
我相信麥克斯 也相信你們
Since you dare to talk big,
既然敢說大話
you must have a plan, right?
代表你們想好對策了吧
Well…
這個嘛…
Because my spells aren't working either,
因為我的咒語也不管用
it seems we can only rely on the sword to attack.
果然只能依賴劍來進攻了
Max, open your mouth.
麥克斯 嘴巴張開
Maximum Drive.
"極限啟動"
This strengthening spell is my trump card, it concentrates all my magical power.
這句強化咒語算是殺手鐧 凝聚了我的所有魔力
Let me say it beforehand, I can only use this move once,
我話說在前頭 這招沒辦法用第二次
settle the fight while your body can still move.
趁身體還能活動時分出勝負吧
Go, Max!
去吧 麥克斯
Finish him while my barrier can still hold!
趁防壁還撐得住時解決掉
You lucky guy.
你這個命大的傢伙
Do you want to be beaten again?
還想繼續挨打嗎
That is…
那是…
So that's how it is. I miss it.
原來如此 來這招啊 真懷念
What's that bitch doing meddling?
那個潑婦 幹嘛多管閒事
Max, can you hear me?
麥克斯 聽得見嗎
Clear as a bell.
聽得一清二楚
You don't have to answer me, this is pre-recorded.
不必回答我 這是預錄的
You know too, right?
你也知道吧
The Maximum Drive spell won't last long.
"極限啟動"這種咒語撐不了多久
You have to settle the fight while your body can still move.
記得在身體還能動的時候分出勝負
But I guess those two understand this very well.
不過那兩人應該也非常明白這一點
Yeah.
是啊
I'm sorry I can't help in person,
抱歉我不能親自去幫忙
but you can't ask a pregnant woman to fight, right?
但總不能叫臨盆的女性去幹架吧
So this time, I'm counting on you.
所以這次就拜託你了
I believe in you, hero.
我相信你 勇者大人
Go teach those two idiots a lesson.
狠狠教訓那兩個蠢蛋一頓吧
Bitch, don't come out to mess up!
臭女人 不要冒出來攪局
Come on, Max, try to stop us.
來吧 麥克斯 來阻止我們啊
Damn it, captain.
可惡 團長
A kid?
小孩子
You're awake. Are you okay?
你醒來了 還好嗎
I'm fine.
朕沒事
You're the young man from the other day, aren't you?
你是那天那個小夥子
How's Max doing?
麥克斯狀況怎麼樣
Do you have a phone on you?
你身上有手機嗎
How about it, Max? Can you beat me?
怎麼樣 麥克斯 有本事打敗我嗎
Do you have any way to defeat me before the Maximum Drive goes off?
你有辦法"極限啟動" 失效之前打敗我嗎
Shut up!
吵死人了
Lie down and be quiet, fool!
安靜睡覺去 蠢貨
Finish him off!
幹掉他
This place needs to be like this…
這裡要這樣…
What the hell is wrong with you guys?
你們到底是怎樣
What the hell are we doing this nonsense for?
我們究竟是為了什麼 在做這種無聊的事
Leo.
雷奧
Isn't the root of all of this because you did something stupid?
一切的起因 不就是因為你幹出那種蠢事嗎
Max.
麥克斯
If you had been willing to help me from the start,
假如你當初就願意協助我
we wouldn't have to fight each other.
我們這些夥伴就不必自相殘殺
What a joke.
開什麼玩笑
How do you plan to clean up this mess?
你們打算怎麼收拾這個局面
What difference will it make if you knock us down, Max?
麥克斯 即使你打倒我們 又會有什麼改變嗎
Are you going to take my place at the mercy of the kingdom?
難道你打算代替我 任憑王國擺布嗎
Yuria, you too.
尤莉亞 妳也一樣
Why is everyone so stupid?
怎麼偏偏都是一群笨蛋
The real fool is me.
愚笨的人是我
Max…
麥…克斯…
Everyone is the same.
每個傢伙都一個樣
They don't understand the pains of others.
完全不懂別人的苦心
I can't take it anymore!
我再也忍無可忍了
Disappear, fools!
通通消失吧 一群笨蛋
What?
什麼
Y-You… Just as I thought…
你…你這傢伙 果然…
It hurts so much, I'm in pain all over.
好痛 全身上下都痛死了
G-Great! The hero won!
太…太好了 勇者贏了
Wait, is it a good thing that Max won?
等等 麥克斯贏了算是好事嗎
What next? What to do next?
然後呢 應該說接下來要怎麼辦
Damn it.
可惡…
The camera.
攝影機…
Is it that one?
是那個嗎
I would like to apologize profusely
關於這次事件
for this incident.
在此致上十二萬分的歉意
My companions have caused you all a great deal of trouble.
我的夥伴給各位造成天大的麻煩
I'm truly sorry.
實在非常抱歉
However, I kindly request…
但是還請…
all of you who are currently watching this
正在觀看影片的各位
to be understanding
能不能網開一面
and considerate in dealing with this matter.
斟酌處理呢
What is he doing?
他到底在做什麼
Could you please think of a way
為了讓這兩個傢伙
to resolve this peacefully
不必再發生衝突
for the sake of these two not having to fight again?
能不能幫忙想辦法圓滿解決呢
Please, everyone.
求求各位幫忙
I'm begging for your help, please.
萬事拜託了 請務必幫幫忙
I'm begging for your help.
萬事拜託了
Please. Please, everyone.
拜託…拜託各位…